KHOMOTSO PRISCA MOGANE

Software Developer

I am a very reliable, self-motivated and enthusiastic individual, with over 4 years working experience designing and developing user-centered applications from initial concept to final, polished deliverable. Strong in design and integration problem-solving skills. I have a passion for information Technology, customer service, a zeal for meeting targets, a keen eye for detail and I consider myself to be an outstanding team player. I am dedicated and dependable individual who possesses excellence.

CONTACT

Randburg, Johannesburg

☑ Priscamogane08@gmail.com



**** 0713959671

EDUCATION

CTU Training Solutions Polokwane IT System Development MCSD - NQF 5 Database Development MCSE BI - NQF 6

CERTIFICATES

Software Development

Database Development

Programming in C# - 70-483

Programming in HTML 5 with

JavaScript and CSS3 - 70-480

Developing Web Applications in

ASP.NET

MCSA: SQL Server 2012/2014

AWS ECS

COMPTIA A+ Microsoft Certified Trainer

Python 3 Programming

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

PROFESSIONAL EVALUATION AND RESEARCH

November 2016 - April 2021 Software Developer

- Developing, maintaining enterprise-wide software solutions.
- Implementing scrum methodologies to approach new projects.
- Developing new applications and upgrading old software systems, integrating new and latest technologies.
- Developing and managing application used by over 200 clients.
- Set up an AWS cloud platform.
- Reporting any faults in the systems and deadlines to the manager.

CTU TRAINING SOLUTION

November 2016 – April 2021 Software Developer

- Presenting courses daily using medias such as PowerPoint and Handouts, Practical Demonstration.
- Helping learners understand the use of Software Development Frameworks, the process of planning, development and deployment of projects.
- Assessing assessments

PETER MOKABA STADIUM

February 2014 - April 2014 Logistics and IT Assistance Manager

> - Working closely with the Logistic manager to manage the Logistic department for the 2014 CAF

SKILLS HIGHLIGHTS

C#, Java, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, 6, Typescript, Rest API, JavaScript, CSS, Git, PHP, Angular, Node.js, HTML, SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Ajax, Redis, Bootstrap, WordPress, Web Design, AWS, UI/UX, Docker, AWS Serverless, Back End Developer, Front End Developer

- Configurations CUP games held at Peter Mokaba Stadium.
- Receiving and Counting stock, distributions of logistics for field, players and stuff members.
- Reporting to Head of Department.
- Assisting with communication devices and installation of software to stuff members Laptops.

REFERENCE

Kevin Majuru - 0670367443 Manager – Professional Evaluation and Research

Daphne Roats – 072 589 6222 Campus Principle – CTU Training Solutions (Polokwane)

Khutso Tsiri – 082 079 8226 Logistic Manager – Peter Mokaba Stadium